你们在干嘛
Hey. Watcha guys doin?
莫妮卡逼我们看《老黄狗》
Monica's making us watch Old Yeller.
那你们在伤心什么
Why are you guys so upset?
这是一部快乐的电影啊
It's Old Yeller, it's a happy movie.
什么
What?
你在胡扯什么
What're you talkin' about?
少来了  快乐家庭养了一只狗  荒野之乐
C'mon, happy family gets a dog, frontier fun.
对呀  菲比  但是结局呢
Yeah but Phoebs, what about the end?
老黄救全家人
What when Yeller saves
于狼口之中  大家皆大欢喜
the family from the wolf and everyone's happy?
那不是结局
That's not the end.
就是  我妈会在那个时候
Yu-huh. That's when my mother would
关掉电视说"剧终"
shut off the TV and say 'The end'.
那它生狂犬病的情节呢
What about the part where he has rabies?
它没有生狂犬病  它生了小宝宝
He doesn't have rabies, he has babies.
我妈说的
That's what my mom said.
菲比  我想你妈妈
Uh, Phoebe, I don't think your mom
不想你看接下来的剧情
would want you to see what's about to happen.
为什么  接下来怎么样
What, what's about to happen?
这部分我从没看过
I've never seen this part before.
崔维斯  你拿枪干什么
Hey, Travis, watcha doin' with that gun?
不  崔维斯  把枪放下来
Oh no, no no Travis, put down the gun.
不要  它是你的伙伴  是你的老黄
No no no no, he he's your buddy, he's your Yeller,
不  剧终  剧终
no, no no, the end, the end.
这是什么虐杀小狗的变态电影
OK, what kind of a sick doggie snuff film is this?
你们吃过了吗
Hey, have you guys eaten,
我跟理查德刚吃完  还有剩菜
because uh, Richard and I just finished and we've got leftovers...
鸡肉跟土豆
Chicken and potatoes...
我穿什么
What am I wearing?...
事实上  只戴了塑胶手套而已
Actually, nothing but rubber gloves.
有一天你会真的一丝不挂
Ya know, one of these times you're gonna really be naked
而我们却不会过来了
and we're not gonna come over.
我有条腿  三块胸跟一根翅膀
Alright, I've got a leg, three breasts and a wing.
那你怎么找得到衣服穿
Well, how do you find clothes that fit?
莫妮卡  我们有个问题
Oh, hey, Monica, we've got a question.
回答无数遍了  对
Alright, for the bizillionth time, yes
我在健身房浴室会看到别的女人
I see other women in shower at the gym,
不  我目不斜视
and no I don't look.
不  不是那个
No, not that one.
我们在想今晚带谁去看尼克斯队的比赛
We're trying to figure out who to bring to the Knicks game tonight,
我们多了一张票
we have an extra ticket.
罗斯不能去  所以要嘛
Yeah, Ross can't go so it's between
就是我朋友艾瑞克·普劳尔  他有口臭
my friend Eric Prower who has breath issues
或是丹  他爱戳人
and Dan with the poking.
你看了那个演出吗
'Did you see that play?
还要啤酒吗  那是史派克·李吗
Do you want some more beer? Is that Spike Lee?'
好啦
Ok.
为什么不问理查德
Hey, why don't you ask Richard?
理查德  如果你多了一张尼克斯队比赛的票
Ok, uh, hey Richard, if you had an extra ticket to the Knicks game
两个朋友  一个有口臭
and you had to choose between a friend who smells
一个会戳到你瘀青  你会选谁
and one who bruises you who would you pick?
对一个超级尼克斯迷来说
Wow. Well being a huge Knicks fan myself,
我想你们应该选一个超级尼克斯迷
I think you should take someone who's a huge Knicks fan.
好的  那就艾瑞克吧
Ok, that's Eric.
乐意效劳  我去点烟
Glad to be of help. Matches.
我是说  你们为什么不请理查德去
I meant, why don't you take Richard to the game?
怎么了
What?
我不知道
I don't know.
少来了  他从来不会乱指乱戳
C'mon. Keeps his fingers to himself
口气永远芳香自然
and he's always minty fresh.
理查德他这个人真的很好啦
I don't know, Richard's really nice and everything,
只是我们跟他不是很熟
uh, it's just that we don't know him really well,
加上他又老
ya know, and plus he's, ya know, old
一些  对某些人来说
er than some people,
但比某些建筑要年轻一些
but, uh, younger than some buildings.
他老一点  那又如何
So what, he's a little older, big deal,
他对我而言很重要
I mean he's important to me.
你们请他的话  他或许会开捷豹车去哦
Ya know if you ask him, he might take you on his Jag.
我们现在要怎么说
How do we say yes now
才不会像是为了搭他的酷车  才邀请他去的
and make it seem like we're not doin' it just to ride in the cool car?
这有点棘手
Ok, this could be tough.
好的  莫妮卡
Ok ok ok ok. Monica,
他开捷豹车来  我们才会带他去
we'll bring him, but only if he takes the Jaguar.
你差点办到了
Ooh, you almost had it.
不  你没问题
No no, you're fine, you're fine.
亲爱的
Hi honey.
你们一定不会相信发生了什么事
Oh you guys are not gonna believe what happened.
什么  什么
What? What?
我们坐在那边地板上玩
Ok, we were sitting over there playing on the floor
他抓住了桌子  把自己拉起来了
and he grabs the table and he pulls himself up.
他把自己拉起来了
He pulled himself up.
他会站
Standing man.
很遗憾你们错过了  但我
I'm sorry you guys missed it but
录下来了  你们要看的话...
I did tape it so it you guys want to see it.
我们知道  他上个星期就会了
Uhh, we know, he already did it last week.
你可以看我们的带子
You can watch our tape if you want.
我真不敢相信
I don't believe this.
我错过了每个第一次
I miss, I miss the first time of everything.
我错过他第一次翻身
I missed, what, the first time he rolled over,
他第一次爬
the first time he crawled.
我还错过了什么  他说话了吗
What else did I miss? Has he spoken yet,
会开车了吗  他有偏好的甜酒吗
is he driving, does he have a favorite liqueur?
他好像也快要会说话了
Actually, he is getting closer on the talking thing.
他还不会说妈妈
He can't quite say mama yet,
可是有一次他说了"也门"
but once he said yemen.
我受不了老是错过
Ooh, I, I'm so sick of missing stuff.
我不要只照顾他一天而已
Ya know, I want him for more than, than a day,
我要照顾他整个周末
I want him for a whole weekend.
听着  我觉得...
No listen , I mean, I feel like-
-太好了  -没问题
- Great. - That would be fine.
真的  我正准备要好好地游说一番呢
Really? I mean, I, I had a whole speach prepared.
讨厌  那会很好玩的
Oh shout, that would have been fun.
你们看到了吗
Oh look, did, did you just see that?
看见没  他刚刚挥手
Did you see? He just waved, he just waved,
他从来没有挥过手  你从来没挥过手
he's never waved before, you've never waved before.
他挥过  好极了
Yes he has. Very good.
菲比  那些是什么
Hey Pheebs, whatcha got there?
《爱情故事》《布里安之歌》《母女情深》
Ok, Love Story, Brian's Song, and Terms of Endearment.
现在只缺《杀戳战场》
Wow, all you need now is The Killing Fields
跟一些鳄梨酱  你就可以狂欢了
and some guacamole and you've got yourself a part-ay.
我跟外婆讲了"老黄狗"那件事
Yeah, I talked to my grandma about the Old Yeller incident,
她说我妈总是不让我们看悲剧电影的结局
and she told me that my mom used to not show us the ends of sad movies
好让我们不用痛苦伤心
to shield us from the pain and sadness.
在她自杀之前
You know, before she killed herself.
他人呢  理查德呢  你们甩了他吗
Hey. Where is he, where's Richard? Did you ditch him?
对  在抢了他的午餐钱  拉了他内裤之后
Yeah right after we stole his lunch money and gave him a wedgie.
你这人怎么搞的  他在停车
What's the matter with you, he's parking the car.
那你们玩得开心吗
So'd you guys have fun?
你的男朋友真的好酷
Your boyfriend is so cool.
是吗
Really?
他让我们开他的捷豹车
Yeah, he let us drive his Jaguar.
乔伊12条街  我15条街
Joey for 12 blocks, me for 15.
他一定最喜欢你了
Wow, he must like you the best.
还有他给
Oh, what about that thing he did
那个领座员小费的方式
when he tipped the guy who showed us to our seats.
连钱都看不到  就像这样
You never even saw the money, it was like this.
钱德勒  谢谢你帮我们带位
Hey Chandler, thanks for showing us to our seats.
不用客气  乔伊  谢谢你帮我停车
You're welcome. Hey Joey, thanks for parking the car.
没问题
No problem.
钱德勒
Hey Chandler...
-我想她们懂了  -好的
- I think they get it. - Okay.
他来了
There's the man.
你越来越行了  对了  我要留着这个
Hey, you're gettin' better. I'm gonna keep this by the way.
好吧  他留下了我的钱
Ok. He kept my dollar.
第一个没有本的周末
So your first whole weekend without Ben,
你们两个要做什么
what're you guys gonna do?
我们要南下去威廉斯堡玩
Uh, we're going down to Colonial Williamsburg.
我大学一个女同学
Yeah, a woman I went to college
刚成为那里第一个女铁匠
with just became the first female blacksmith down there.
知道吗
Well, ya know,
威廉斯堡那边是有点落伍了
they're a little behind the times in Colonial Williamsburg.
我们最好在掉眼泪之前走了
Think I better go before mommy starts weeping.
-拜  -我们爱你
- Bye. - We love you.
我们爱你  拜
We love you. Bye.
好好玩
Have a good time.
-好了  本  -罗斯
- Ok, Ben. - Ross.
什么事
Yeah?
看
Look.
乔伊  你知道我们看得到你吗
Joey, do you know we can see you from here?
为什么理查德抽起这个比我酷那么多
How come Richard looks so much cooler with one of these than me?
首先  或许你要点燃
Well for starters, you may want to light it
还有放下那支刮铲
and lose the spatula.
你想模仿理查德  我觉得很可爱
You know what, I think it's cute, you trying to be more like Richard.
也不是这样  只是不要不像他
Not like him, per-se, just not un-like him.
看  是以前叫钱德勒的那个艺术家
Look it's the artist formerly known as Chandler.
我不过是想试试看
Just tryin' somethin' here, ya know.
乔伊  你为什么不留胡子
So Joey, why didn't you grow a moustache?
我们丢硬币决定的
Oh we flipped for it.
我丢到抽雪茄  他丢到留胡子
I got the cigar, he got the moustache.
我想我们都留的话  会有点蠢啦
Figured if we both grew it, we'd look like dorks.
是呀  你们真是躲过了一劫
Yeah, you really sidestepped that land mine.
我们得走了  我答应理查德在楼下见
Hey listen, we've gotta go, I promised Richard we'd meet him downstairs.
你们要见理查德吗
You're meeting Richard?
对  我们要去看冰球赛
Yeah, we're goin' to a Ranger game.
他没告诉你吗
Yeah, didn't he tell ya?
他告诉我  他跟哥们出去
Well, he told me he was going out with the guys,
我只是不知道哥们是你们
I just didn't know that you were the guys.
你听到了吗  我们是哥们
You hear that? We're the guys.
我们是哥们
We're the guys.
钱德勒留那胡子  像不像西维亚姑妈
With that moustache doesn't Chandler remind you of Aunt Sylvia?
谢谢
Thank you.
我们来拜访
Hi, we're visitiing.
是小本跟他爹爹
It's Ben and his da-da.
爹爹
Da-da.
你会说爹爹吗
Can you say da-da?
听着  反正我会告诉你妈咪们你说了
Look, I'm gonna tell your momies you said it anyway
你好歹试试啊
so you might as well try.
运气不好
No luck huh?
不好  之前他发了一个"二"的音
Naa. A while ago I got a sah out of him,
我想
which I thought, ya know,
那也可以勉强说是二保姆的意思
might turn into sah-condary caregiver but...
帮我抱一下  好吗
Hey, would you uh, would you hold him for a sec,
我得把这个拿下来
'cause I, I gotta take this off.
好的
Oh, yeah sure, Ok.
你在干什么
What're you doing?
我在抱本啊
Uh, I'm holding Ben.
他是个宝宝  不是炸弹
Yeah, well, he's a baby not a bomb.
知道
Okay.
你可以像抱橄榄球那样抱他
Well just hold him like you'd hold a football.
我就是这样抱橄榄球的
This is how I would hold a football.
好吧  这样  对了
Ok, here, here. There we go.
对不起  我不太会带孩子
Ok, I'm sorry, I'm just not very good with babies.
我没接触过他们
I mean I haven't been around them,
自我长大以后啦
I mean, you know, since I was one.
没关系  没什么大不了的
It's alright, it's no big deal.
真的
Really?
当然了
Yeah, definitely,
我相信如果抱我们的宝宝
I'm sure you'll feel totally different
你的感觉会完全不同
when it's our baby.
什么
What?
你会考虑这样的事吗
You think about stuff like that?
对
Uhh, yeah.
我是说  事实上
I mean, actually
我想我们会有  有两个宝宝
I kinda think that we'll have, we'll have two babies.
两个宝宝
Two, two babies?
对  一男一女
Yeah. Ya know, a boy and a girl.
我希望先有女孩
Hopefully the girl will come first
这样本不会觉得有太大的竞争
so Ben here won't feel too competitive.
那接下来呢
Then what's gonna happen?
我们不希望孩子在城市里长大
Well, we won't wanna raise kids in the city
所以我们或许会搬到史卡戴区
so we'll probably move to uh, Scarsdale.
我是想着
Yeah, that way I figure,
这样住得离我们的父母够远
ya know, we'll be far enough away from our parents
所以不用常常看到他们
that we don't have to see them all the time but
但又不会太远  随时可以请他们来带小孩
close enough that they can come over and babysit whenever we want.
没错  我知道那里的税要比
And yes, I know, the taxes are a little higher than, let's say,
拿骚县高一点  但教学制度据说非常棒
Nassau county but the school system's supposedly great.
哇  哇  太棒了
Wow. Wow, that's great. Great.
你知道吗
Ok, wow, you know what.
我休息时间结束了
I'm off my break now so uh,
所以你拿着这个
um here you take this and um,
我要去帮这些好人倒咖啡了
I am gonna go pour these very nice people some coffee.
你瞧瞧  我没有咖啡壶
Ok. Oh look at that, I don't have a pot.
我没有咖啡壶
I don't have a pot. Well, hey,
或许我家里有一个
maybe I've got one at home,
或在史卡戴区  那是门吗
or in Scarsdale. Hey is that a door?
瑞秋
Rach.
菲比  怎么了
Hey Pheebs, what's happening?
谋杀  癌症
Oh, ok, murder, cancer,
足球队在安第斯山脉吃来吃去
soccer teams eating each other in the Andes.
你看了电影了
So you watched the movies huh?
这个世界到底怎么了
Uh huh, what is happening to the world?
我是说  ET走了
I mean, no no no, 'cause ET leaves,
洛基输了  夏洛特死了
and and Rocky loses, Charlotte dies.
哪个夏洛特
Charlotte who?
织网那个  蜘蛛  它死了
With the web, the spider she dies, she does.
它生了宝宝后就死了
She has babies and dies.
那就像  "欢迎从医院回来"  倒地毙命
It's like ya know, hey welcome home from the hospital, thud.
想不想心情好一些
Alright, you wanna feel better?
当然
Yeah.
好的  看这个
Ok, here, watch this.
《美好人生》  这个我听说过
It's a Wonderful Life. Yes I've heard of this.
所以没问题  片名说明了一切
So you can't lose, it's there in the title.
包你美好的不得了
Wonderfullness is baked right in.
拜托  我差点就被《扬基的骄傲》给骗了
Please, I almost fell for that with, uh, Pride of the Yankees,
我以为我要看的是  扬基队的骄傲
I thought I was gonna see a film about Yankee pride
然后  那个球员得了路葛瑞症
and then, boom, the guy gets Lou Gehrig's disease.
那个球员就叫路葛瑞  你没预感吗
Uh, the guy was Lou Gehrig. Didn't you kinda see it coming?
菲比  你看就是了
Phoebe, just watch that,
我保证能让你恢复对人类的信心
I promise it will resotre all your faith in humanity.
大个儿  比赛时间到了
Hey, big guy, game time.
好  马上来
Hey, be right there.
有比赛吗
There's a game?
对  我刚从店里买了挑竹签玩具回来
Uh, yeah, I just got my pick-up sticks back from the shop.
带着你的铁胆来
Bring your nerves of steel.
是篮球季后赛
It's the basketball playoffs.
亲爱的  你这样很好
Listen, um honey, I appreciate this
但是你不用为了我跟他们混
but you don't have to keep hanging out with them for me,
反正他们两个可以作伴
I mean, they have each other.
不  亲爱的  别担心
Oh, no, honey, I mean, don't worry,
我很喜欢跟他们玩
I like hanging out with those guys.
很有趣  他们跟我别的朋友不同
It's fun for me. They're different than my other friends,
他们不会一见面就说
they don't start sentences with,
你知道谁铲雪时死了吗
'You know who just died shoveling snow?'
很好  那就去吧  加油  尼克斯队
Alright that's great, then just go. Go Knicks.
是大学篮球季后赛
Uh, it's the college playoffs.
加油  瓦萨队
Oh, then go Vassar.
没他们
Uh, they're not in it.
-那就加油吧  -好
- Ok, then just go. - Okay.
我为什么要那么在意呢
Oh, why does this bother me so much?
我并不想当那种要男友
I mean I don't wanna be one of those people who tells their boyfriend
24小时都跟她们在一起的人
they wanna spend 24 hours a day with them.
对呀
Sure.
只是他空闲的时间不多
It's just that he doesn't have that much free time, ya know,
我不知道  我该怎么办
and I don't know, what do I do?
有关系吗  你始终都会死
Does it matter? You're ultimately just gonna die
或离婚  或枪杀你的宠物
or get divorced or have to blow your pets head off.
我也是
Me too.
我有个问题  理查德又跟他们有安排了
I've got a question. Richard made plans again with the guys.
罗斯刚安排好了整个世纪呢
Yeah well, Ross just made plans for the whole century.
我还是回房去看《时尚》杂志吧
Ya know what, I think I'm gonna go to my room and read Cosmo,
或许会读到什么有用的
maybe there's something helpful in there.
至少也许可以学会怎样用剩下的
If not, at least maybe I can learn how to do an at home bikini
圣诞蜡烛自己做比基尼部位除毛
wax with leftover Christmas candles.
你刚刚是怎么回事
Ok, what the hell happened back there?
不知道  你告诉我吧
I don't know, you tell me.
我刚刚还像抱橄榄球一样抱着本
One minute I'm holding Ben like a football,
接下来我就有两个孩子
the next thing I know, I've got two kids,
住在史卡戴区  抱怨税太高
I'm living in Scarsdale complaining about the taxes.
抱歉  我就是爱东想西想
Well I'm sorry, I think about stuff.
我是说  工作的时候
Ya know, I mean, you're at work,
一边弄骨头就会一边乱想嘛
you're assembling bones, your mind wanders.
罗斯  你计划了我们以后二十年的生活
Ross, you have planned out the next 20 years of our lives,
我们才约会六周而已
we've been dating for six weeks.
拜托  你从不想将来的事吗
C'mon, what, you never think about our future?
想  但我想的是明晚
Yes, but I, I think about who's apartment
我们住谁那边好
we're gonna sleep at tomorrow night and,
下个周六晚上  我们去哪里吃晚饭
and where we're gonna have dinner next Saturday night.
我不会去想  我们的孩子叫什么名字
I do not think about what our childrens' names are gonna be.
你知道我们的孩子会叫什么名字
You know what our childrens names are gonna be.
不是啦  我只是  我看到一本书
No, no, I mean, ya know, I, I read a book
里头有个女孩叫艾蜜莉
and there was a girl named Emily
我觉得  我觉得这名字还不错
and I thought, I thought that might be good.
什么书
What was the book?
《儿童命名大全》
The big book of childrens' names.
罗斯  你听着  我们在一起非常棒
Ok, Ross, Ross, ok listen, what we have is amazing.
是啊
Yeah.
但我不要别人为我决定好一切
But I do not want to have everything decided for me.
我那样过一辈子了
I spent my whole life like that.
我跟巴瑞就是那样  这是我离开的原因之一
It's what I had with Barry, that was one of the reasons I left.
我喜欢有未知
I, I like not knowing right now
如果这样吓着了你  那很抱歉
and I'm sorry if that scares you
但如果你要跟我在一起  你只能接受
but if you want to be with me you are gonna have to deal with that.
好  很好
Ok fine.
谢谢
Thank you.
还没完呢
We're not done.
那我不知道
I didn't know that.
你必须明白
Ok, then you're gonna have to understand that
跟你在一起的人不会停止
you're with a guy who's not gonna stop planning
去计划他跟你的未来
his future with you because
因为他知道我们最后会在一起
he knows that we're gonna end up together
如果你害怕了  很不幸
and if that scares you, tough,
因为你必须学会接受
'cause you're gonna have to deal with that.
很好  我会的
Fine, I will.
好  因为我爱你
Good, 'cause I love you.
我也爱你
Well I love you too.
我们第一次互相说我爱你
Well that's the first time we've said that.
没错
Yes it is.
那我就要亲你了
Well, I'm gonna kiss you.
最好是这样
Well you better.
嘿  谢谢你给我的电影建议
Hey. Oh thanks for the great movie tip.
你喜欢吗
Did you like it?
喜欢  我不知道看到哪里最开心
Oh yeah. You know, I don't know if I was happier
乔治·贝利的家族企业破产呢
when um George Bailey destroyed the family business
还是唐娜·瑞德哭泣
or um, Donna Reid cried,
或坏蛋药剂师害他耳朵流血
or when the mean pharmacist made his ear bleed.
好吧  我选耳朵流血
Alright, I'll give you the ear thing
但你不觉得结局很好吗
but don't you think the ending was pretty wonderful?
我根本没看结局  我太沮丧了
I didn't watch the ending, I was too depressed.
剧情越来越惨
It just kept getting worse and worse,
这电影应该叫  《人生真惨
it should have been called, "It's a sucky life
就在你觉得无法更惨时  更惨了》
and just when you think it can't suck any more it does."
守门员踢挡救球  成功
Kick save and... denied.
但他抢回来  传到中间  起脚
But... he gets it back, pass to the middle, lines it up and...
进  太棒了
BAM! Yes!
那球还可以踢得更漂亮些吗
Could that shot be any prettier?
老兄  你真厉害
Man you are incredible.
我们大学时也有这玩意儿
Well, we had a table in college.
我不知道原来19世纪就有桌上足球了
Oh really, I didn't know they had foosball in the 1800's.
对了  你的胡子不错
Nice moustache by the way.
青春期一到就会茂盛起来的
When puberty hits that thing's really gonna kick in.
亲爱的  我也不想太像个好太太
Honey. Uh, not to sound too Florence Henderson
但晚餐做好了
but, dinner's on the table.
好的  再玩一下
Ok, just one more point.
得分  可以走了吗
Score! Now can we go?
看吧  所以我们才不让她玩
See, that's why we don't let her play.
一切都还好吧
Is everything all right?
听我说  别跟他生气  是我们的错
Oh hey listen, don't be mad at him, it's our fault.
我们占了他太多时间了
I'm sorry we've been hoggin so much of his time.
是呀  跟他一起玩真的是很棒
Yeah, he's just really great to hang around with.
-这个嘛  -不  说真的
- Well. - No no, seriously,
我跟钱德勒刚才还在说
Chandler and I were just talkin about this.
他比我们的老爸酷多了
He is so much cooler than our dads.
我是说我们老爸也还好啦
I mean, you know, our dad's are ok, ya know,
可是理查德...  你踢我干什么
but Richard is just- ow, ow. What are you kickin me for?
我正在讲话呢
Huh? I'm tryin to talk here.
你们觉得我是父字辈的吗
Uh, you guys see me as a dad?
对呀
Oh yeah.
不
No.
不是
你很显然不了解
Your just, your just clearly not familiar
我们年轻人的用语
with our young persons vernacular.
我们说老爸  其实是指兄弟
See, when we say dad, we mean buddy.
是伙伴的意思
We mean pal.
是啊
Uh-huh, yeah.
说真的  乔伊是我老爸
No no, seriously, Joey's my dad,
莫妮卡是我老爸
Monica's my dad.
我们公司里还有一些人是我老爸
I've even got some dads down at work.
没问题
That's fine.
你们另一个老爸跟我  要去过一个浪漫之夜
Well, your other dad and I are gonna go have a romantic evening
孩子们  我们改天见了
and I guess I'll just see you kids around.
晚安了
Nighty-nite.
你不是老爸  你不是老爸
You're not a dad. You're not a dad.
不是老爸
Not a dad.
真不敢相信你干的好事
I can't believe you got us into trouble.
你还好吗
So are you ok?
很好
Yeah,
我只是觉得自己好老
just, I feel like I'm about a hundred.
我还以为我跟他们一样
I thought I was just one of the guys.
过来  我会让你觉得你跟他们一样
Come here. I'll make you feel like one of the guys.
对一个很酷的人来说  你玩桌上足球烂透了
You know for a really cool guy, you suck at foosball.
说什么呢  我痛宰了他们
What're you talkin' about, I was killin' 'em.
他们也很烂
Yeah, well they suck too.
然后你把便便尿布
Ok, and then you take the poopie diaper
丢到便便尿布桶里去
and you put it in the poopie diaper pail.
罗斯你要知道  美其名为便便尿布
Ok Ross, just so you know, calling it a poopie diaper
并不会让这个过程更可爱
doesn't make this process any cuter.
-喂  -是我们
- Hello? - It's us.
上来吧  我去准备他其它的东西
Come on up. I'm gonna get the rest of his stuff together.
我们做得到的  是不是  本
Ok, we can do this now, can't we Ben?
对  我们可以  我们可以的
Yes we can, yes we can.
好了  我成功了  我成功了
There. I did it. I did it.
你瞧瞧  紧紧的包在屁屁上
Look at that, oh, stays on and everything.
嗨
Hi.
抱歉  你刚刚说什么
I'm sorry, what did you just say?
你刚刚说"嗨"吗
Did you just say hi?
天啊  罗斯  罗斯  本刚刚说了"嗨"
Oh my God, Ross, Ross, Ben just said 'Hi'.
-什么  -本刚说了"嗨"
- Wha, what? - Ben just said hi.
什么  "嗨"那个字吗
What, the word hi?
不  我的嗨舅舅
Ye-, no, my Uncle Hi.
这下可好  我又错过了  我错过了一切
Great, great, and I miss that too, I miss everything.
抱歉  我猜我太有魅力了
Oh, I'm sorry, I guess I just bring it out in him.
你们好
Hello.
我好想你  过来吧  本
I miss you so much, come here Ben.
知道吗  本刚说了第一个字
Guess what. Ben just said his first word.
他说什么了
What did he say?
什么嗨不嗨的
Something about hi.
真是令人兴奋
That's so exciting.
妈咪好骄傲哦
Mommy is so proud of you.
嗨
Hi.
Hi?
事实上比较像这样  嗨
You know, actually it's more like, hi.
这可能要玩很久
Ok, this could go on for a while.
计程车还在楼下等我们呢
We've got a cab waiting downstairs.
真有意思
Well, this was fun.
改天一定要再来一次  本  你说呢
We should really do it again sometime, Ben wha'dya say?
好的  我下次照顾他是...
Ok. Alright so I've got him.
星期二
Tuesday.
好的  星期二  再见了
Tuesday right. Ok, bye you guys.
保重
Take care.
拜  本
Bye Ben.
拜
Bye.
他刚刚  他  他刚刚说拜吗
Did, did he just, did he, did he just say, he said bye.
他说拜  你对我说拜  他对我说拜
He said bye. You said, you said bye to me. You said bye to me.
我已经可以想象他上大学的样子了
Suddenly I'm seeing him go off to college.
我们得走了  计程车在楼下等
We've gotta go, we've got that cab downstairs.
好的  好的
Alright, alright, ok.
-回见了  -好的
- See you later. - All right.
-拜  -拜
- Bye. - Bye.
拜
Bye.
看我挖的这个洞好深啊
Oh wow, look at this nice deep hole I've been digging.
伯特  这洞是不是挖得很好
Hey Bert, isn't this a nice hole here. Hey.
本  这一段是讲
Ok, Ben, this is the part
厄尼把伯特埋在沙里  找不到他了
where Ernie buries Bert in the sand and can't find him.
我已经先看过了
Now, I've looked ahead on the tape
他后来有找到他
and he does find him again.
可是  在那之前呢
But, ok, before that happens,
会先有一些让人很难受的
there's some pretty rough goin' for a while
可是我想我们挺得住
but I think we can handle it.
这些只是字母而已
And, there's just the alphabet
可我们知道结局会很好的
but we know that ends well so.
好的  继续了
Ok, here we go.
伯特  伯特...
Bert, Bert. Bert.
我朋友伯特怎么了
Hey, what happened to my friend Bert?
他刚刚还在这里
He was here just a moment ago.
不好  我的好朋友伯特不见了
Oh no, my old friend Bert is lost.
我真高兴你在这里
Oh, I'm so glad you're here.